ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials
1935-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5619 AV
36.06 cubic feet
36.1 linear ft.
Slides (photographs), audiovisual materials.
This collection contains mostly "media type tapes" received from the Kamber Group. However, there are also cassette (audio) tapes, video tapes and movie films included.
5675112
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 08, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 21, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 C-S MB: ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman Additional Books, Memorabilia, and Files 5619 F: ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 G: ACTWU Graphics 5619 MB: ACTWU Memorabilia Collection 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/001: ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004 fiche: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Speeches on Microfiche 5619/005: ACWA Bessie Hillman Papers 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/008: ACWA Rieve-Pollock Foundation Files 5619/009: ACTWU Operations Department Sidney Hillman Awards Files 5619/010: ACWA Jacob Potofsky files 5619/011: ACTWU Southern Regional Joint Board Files 5619/012: ACTWU Company Files 5619/013: ACTWU Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files 5619/015: ACTWU Department of Occupational Safety and Health Files
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States.; Clothing industry -- United States.; Textile industry-- United States.; Textile workers-- Labor unions -- United States.; Byssinosis (Brown Lung Disease); Strikes and lockouts; Finlay, Murray; Sutton, Crystal Lee; J. P. Stevens; Farah Slacks; Amalgamated Bank of New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Legislative Department.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
5675112
- Shopping for Kid's Clothing, 1981; 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Item No. V1
- Shopping for Kid's Clothing, 1981; 1 (Box 1)
  Item No. V1 ---
- Unused Power, 2 (Box 1)
  Item No. V2
- ACTWU Second Continental Congress, 1981; 3 (Box 1)
  Item No. V3
- Campaign for Americas Future, 1984; 4 (Box 1)
  Item No. V4
- Not Another Generation, 1982; 5 (Box 1)
  Item No. V5
- Labor in the South, NBC Nightly News, 1979; 6 (Box 1)
  Item No. V6
- The Issue is Life and Breath, 7 (Box 1)
  Item No. V7 (copy 1)
- The Issue is Life and Breath, 8 (Box 1)
  Item No. V7 (copy 2)
- The Southern Labor Movement, American Black Forum, 1980; 9 (Box 1)
  Item No. V8
- Jerry Lewis Telethon, 1984; 10 (Box 1)
  Item No. V9
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers-- CBS TV, 1983; 11 (Box 1)
  Item No. V10
- Textiles, 1984; 12 (Box 1)
  Item No. V11
- Labor & Labor Day NBC TV, 1984; 13 (Box 1)
  Item No. V12
- Today Show, Lichtenberg campaign, 1988; 1 (Box 2)
  Item No. V13 -- moved from 5619 AV, box 1 in reorganization
- 60 Minutes, 1984; 2 (Box 2)
  Item No. V14 -- moved from 5619 AV box 1 in reorganization
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers: WOR TV, 1983; 3 (Box 2)
  Item No. V15 -- moved from 5619 AV box 1 in reorganization
- American Corporations in Mexico; Mexican Labor; 60 Minutes, 1984; 4 (Box 2)
  Item No. V16 -- moved from 5619 AV box 1 in reorganization
- Congressional Hearing on Worker Dislocation, 1983; 5 (Box 2)
  Moved from box 1 in reorganization
- Keeping On: Americas Playhouse, NET TV, 1983; 6 (Box 2)
  Moved from 5619 AV box 1 in reorganization -- Beta Format
- Firing Line with Jerry Wurf, 1979; 7 (Box 2)
  Moved from 5619 AV box 1 in reorganization - Beta format
- Pres. Finley addresses ACTWU, 1984; 8 (Box 2)
  Item No. 17
- Today in Chicago: Subject: Murray Finley, 1982; 9 (Box 2)
  Item No. V18
- Labor Conference Interview: Glenn Watts, Murray Finley, 1982; 10 (Box 2)
  Item No. V19
- Labor Conference Interview: Glenn Watts, Murray Finley, 1982; 11 (Box 2)
  Item No. V20
- Chicago Today: Subject: Murray Finley, 1982; 12 (Box 2)
  Item No. V21
- Nightly News, Subject: Murray Finley, 1982; 13 (Box 2)
  Item No. V22
- Murray Finley with Dr. Philip Dolce and Henry Graff, 1982; 14 (Box 2)
  Item No. V71
- Brown Lung Hearings, 1977; 15 (Box 2)
  Item No. V23 - moved from 5619 AV box 3 in reorganization
- Brown Lung, 60 Minutes, 1979; 16 (Box 2)
  Item No. V24 -- moved from 5619 AV box 3
- Brown Lung Victim Actuality, 1 (Box 3)
  Item No. V25
- Brown Lung Victim Actuality, 2 (Box 3)
  Item No. V25 -- (copy 2)
- J. P. Stevens: McNeil/Lehrer Report, 1977; 3 (Box 3)
  Item No. V26
- News segments on Brown Lung Victims' vigil, 1981; 4 (Box 3)
  Item No. V27
- Brown Lung rally, ACTWU footage, 5 (Box 3)
  Item No. V28
- OSHA Brown Lung, 1979; 6 (Box 3)
  Item No. V29
- Amalgamated/Beck ABC TV, 1983; 7 (Box 3)
  Item No. V30
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally Tape 1, 1979; 8 (Box 3)
  Item No. V31
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally Tape 2, 1979; 9 (Box 3)
  Item No. V32
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally Tape 3, 1979; 10 (Box 3)
  Item No. V33
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally Tape 4, 1979; 11 (Box 3)
  Item No. V34
- D.F. Interview Martin Luther King Sr., 1977; 12 (Box 3)
  U-Matic S
- J. P. Stevens Protest, Martin Luther King Sr., 1977; 13 (Box 3)
- NBC: Union movement in South, 1979; 14 (Box 3)
- J. P. Stevens, 1978; 15 (Box 3)
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 1, 1 (Box 4)
  Item No. V35
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 2, 2 (Box 4)
  Item No. V36
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 3, 3 (Box 4)
  Item No. V37
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 4, 4 (Box 4)
  Item No. V38
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 5, 5 (Box 4)
  Item No. V39
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 6, 6 (Box 4)
  Item No. V40
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 7, 7 (Box 4)
  Item No. V41
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 8, 8 (Box 4)
  Item No. V42
- J. P. Stevens Campaign - tape 9, 9 (Box 4)
  Item No. V43
- Rally for Justice, 1980; 10 (Box 4)
  Item No. V44
- Unlabeled except for the Item No. V45, 11 (Box 4)
  Item No. V44. U-Matic S - format
- Video TV Clips, Labor Day, 1982; 1 (Box 5)
  Item No. V46
- Labor, 1982; 2 (Box 5)
  Item No. V47
- In House Polling: A New Technique for Organizing, 3 (Box 5)
  Item No. V48
- "St. Louis Illustrated" Crystal Lee Sutton, 1980; 4 (Box 5)
  Item No. V49
- Keeping On: American Playhouse, 1983; 5 (Box 5)
  Item No. V50
- And that's how we did in the Mill: Women in the Lowell Textile Mills, 6 (Box 5)
  Item No. V51
- Unused Power, 7 (Box 5)
  Item No. V52
- The Golden Door, 8 (Box 5)
  Item No. V53
- Amalgamated Bank, CNN TV, 9 (Box 5)
  Item No. V54
- USCEA Video newsletter, 1983; 10 (Box 5)
  Item No. V55
- Their Life's Sweat, 1979; 11 (Box 5)
  Item No. V56
- Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers, 12 (Box 5)
  Item No. V57
- Scott M Hoyman, ACTWU, 1984; 13 (Box 5)
  Item No. V58
- Political spots, historical survey, 14 (Box 5)
- Unlabeled tape, 1 (Box 6)
  Item No. V59
- Hershowitz home movies; Amalgamated membership picnic, 2 (Box 6)
- News footage, 3 (Box 6)
  from: Neil Waldman, Director, News Film-Videotape Library
- Unlabeled tape, 4 (Box 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 5 (Box 6)
  Item No. V60
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 6 (Box 6)
  Item No. V60; moved from box 8 to box 6 during reorganization of the collection
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 7 (Box 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 8 (Box 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 9 (Box 6)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 10 (Box 6)
  Item No. 60; moved from box 8 to box 6 during reorganization of the collection
- Charles Sallee Memorial, 11 (Box 6)
  Item No. V61; moved from box 8 to box 6 in reorganization of collection
- Murray Finley: A Man and a Union, 12 (Box 6)
  Item No. V62; moved from box 8 to box 6 in reorganization of collection
- Murray Finley: A Man and a Union, 13 (Box 6)
- National Co-Op Bank, 1987 Annual meeting presentation, 14 (Box 6)
  Item No. V63; moved from box 8 to box 6 in reorganization of collection
- One Man's Courage & A Union's Faith: Tom Rumore and the New York Joint Board, 1 (Box 7)
  Item No. V64; moved from box 8 to box 7 in reorganization of collection
- They'll Never Keep Us Down: The story of the United Mine Workers of America Struggle at the Pittston Company, 2 (Box 7)
  Item No. V65; moved from box 8 to box 7 in reorganization of collection
- New York ACTWU in Action!, 3 (Box 7)
  Item No. V66; moved from box 8 to box 7 in reorganization of collection
- Breakthrough in New York!, 4 (Box 7)
  Item No. V67; moved from box 8 to box 7 in reorganization of collection
- New York ACTWU in Action!, 5 (Box 7)
- The Inheritance written by Millard Lampell, produced and directed by Harold Mayer, 1964, 6 (Box 7)
  Item No. V68; moved from box 8 to box 7 in reorganization of collection
- Amalgamated Life, I, 1964; 7 (Box 7)
  IV, not with collection when reorganized. These tapes were moved from box 8 to box 7 during reorganization.
- Amalgamated Life II, 1988; 8 (Box 7)
- Amalgamated Life III, 9 (Box 7)
- Interview on role of unions in society (1988), 10 (Box 7)
  Interviews on role of unions in society. Charleston
- Dinkins, 11 (Box 7)
  'Dinkins' was all the labelling on the tape box
- ACTWU/Actor Michael Freed (Master Dub), 1 (Box 8)
  moved from box 9 to box 8 during the reorganization of the collection
- Actor / Master Dub (Short-Loevy Sec. Treas.), 2 (Box 8)
- NY ACTWU Interviews, 3 (Box 8)
- Social Security: 50 Years Strong, 4 (Box 8)
  Item No. V69; moved from box 9 to box 8 during the reorganization of the collection
- Our Job's Not Done, 5 (Box 8)
  Item No. V72; moved from box 9 to box 8 during the reorganization of the collection
- Dream Continues, 6 (Box 8)
  Item No. V70 - moved from box 9 to box 8 during reorganization of collection
- Dream Continues, 7 (Box 8)
  Item No. V70; moved from box 9 to box 8 during reorganization of collection
- Dream Continues, 8 (Box 8)
- Bishop Metzger, 9 (Box 8)
  moved from box 19 to box 8 during reorganization of collection
- Liberty: Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers, 10 (Box 8)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Connecticut. Congresswoman Johnson, District 6, 11 (Box 8)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 12 (Box 8)
  Moved from box 19 to box 8 during reorganization of collection
- Ed Asner Narration, Roll 1, 13 (Box 8)
- Ed Asner Narration, Roll 2, 14 (Box 8)
- Ed Asner Narration, Roll 3, 15 (Box 8)
- Ed Asner Narration, Roll 4, 16 (Box 8)
  moved from box 19 to box 8 during reorganization of the collection
- Ed Asner Narration, Final edited take, outtakes, 17 (Box 8)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Ohio, Congressman Luken, District 1, 18 (Box 8)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman McHugh, District 28, 19 (Box 8)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman McHugh, District 28, 20 (Box 8)
  moved from box 19 to box 8 during the reorganization of the collection
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 21 (Box 8)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 22 (Box 8)
  moved to box 19 from box 8 during the reorganization of the collection
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Connecticut, Congressman Rowland, District 5, 1 (Box 9)
  moved from box 19 to box 9 during reorganization of the collection
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Indiana, Senators Lugar and Quayle, Congressman Hamilton, District 9, 2 (Box 9)
  moved from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization of the collection
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 3 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Indiana, with Senators Lugar and Quayle, Congressman Sharp, District 2, 4 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 5 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman LaFalce, District 32, 6 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Gunderson, District 3, 7 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Rhode Island, Senator Chafee, 8 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Vermont, Senator Stafford and Congressman Jeffords, 9 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 10 (Box 9)
- "Contract, Contract" The Labor Theater, 11 (Box 9)
- Bishop Metzger, 12 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 13 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman Boehlert, District 25, 14 (Box 9)
- TWUA, 15 (Box 9)
  moved from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization o of the collection
- Liberty ACTWU spot, 16 (Box 9)
- Liberty ACTWU spot, 17 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Florida, Senator Chiles and Congressman McKay, 18 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New Jersey, Senator Bradley and Congressman Saxton, District 13, 19 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman Boehlert, District 25, 20 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman LaFalce, District 32, 21 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Ohio, Congressman Luken, District 1, 22 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: New York, Congressman LaFalce, District 32, 23 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Florida, Senator Chiles and Congressman McKay, 24 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Florida, Senator Chiles and Congressman McKay, 25 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 26 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Indiana, with Senators Lugar and Quayle, Congressman Sharp, District 2, 27 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Wisconsin, Congressman Kleczka, District 4, 28 (Box 9)
- Statue of Liberty Spot: Ohio, Congressman Luken, District 1, 29 (Box 9)
- ACTWU Rally (6 reels), 1 (Box 10)
  Tape #1 (pt.1-2); Tape #2 (pt.1-2); Tape #3 (pt.1-2) -- moved from box 20 to box 10 during the reorganization of the collection
- J. P. Stevens Audio Tapes; Roanoke Rapids (5 Reels), 2 (Box 10)
  Tape #1-5; moved from box 20 to box 10 during the reorganization of the collection
- Victor Riesel News Program; Howard D., 1971; 3 (Box 10)
  moved from box 20 to box 10 during the reorganization of the collection
- J for Jobs Jimmy Rogers, 1986; 4 (Box 10)
- Farah Slacks, Strike Settlement and Aftermath Interview with Sol Brandzel, Mr. William A. Lee and Brother Pius Alexius with Jim Frank, 5 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - Import Hearing, 1985; 6 (Box 10)
- Unlabeled reel, 7 (Box 10)
  moved from box 20 to box 10 during reorganization of the collection
- Jean Piat, 8 (Box 10)
- The Dream Continues - final Music Track, Horatio Alger Sequence, 9 (Box 10)
- Kamber Group "The Dream Continues" new trax music (4-2-1985), 10 (Box 10)
- JR Inserts - ACTWU Narration, 11 (Box 10)
- ACTWU music, 12 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - Dialog - JR, 13 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - JR Narration, 14 (Box 10)
- ACTWU- Dialog - New March, 15 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - Scratch Narration, 16 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - Voices, 17 (Box 10)
- Kamber - Dream Continues. 4-7-1985: 1.Opening - no vocal; 2.Vocals, 18 (Box 10)
- The Dream Continues / Happy Days / Remember: ACTWU Music, 19 (Box 10)
- [missing] - Dec. 2017, 1985; 20 (Box 10)
- ACTWU Dialog - New 1985 March, 21 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - JR Narration - June 1985, 22 (Box 10)
- ACTWU - JR Narration - June 1985, 1 (Box 11)
  moved from box 20 to box 11 during the reorganization of the collection
- ACTWU- The Dream Continues - (15 IPS) - New Changes - 4-1-1985, 2 (Box 11)
- New Opening & Industrial: 4-3-1985, 3 (Box 11)
- Final Tracks - Vocal Pieces - Patti - Opening, Remember, Finale, 1985; 4 (Box 11)
- Unlabeled tape, 5 (Box 11)
- The Dream Continues - Opening Music, 6 (Box 11)
- Kamber Group - the Dream Continues - Scenes 3-53 - Original recording, 7 (Box 11)
- Kamber Group - The Dream Continues - Scenes 232-End; includes Eugene Debs at Head and Chants at TAK - Original recording (3-28-1985), 8 (Box 11)
- Kamber Group - The Dream Continues - Scenes 102-175: Original Recording (3-28-1985), 9 (Box 11)
- Kamber Group - The Dream continues - Scenes 54A-101: Original recording -- (3-28-1985), 10 (Box 11)
- ACTWU - Final Narration - R-1, 11 (Box 11)
- The Dream Continues - Reel one Music: Original music (2-18-1985), 12 (Box 11)
- ACTWU - Final Narration - R-2, 13 (Box 11)
- Kamber Group - The Dream Continues - Scenes 176-230A: Original recording (3-28-1985), 14 (Box 11)
- ACTWU - Facing Crisis, Fighting Back (121 Slides), 34 (Box 11)
  moved from box 22 to box 11 during the reorganization of the collection
- Farah Strike (7/23/2004), 35 (Box 11)
  moved from box 23 to box 11 during the reorganization of the collection
- Town Meeting Labor Issues, Arthur A. Coia (August 30, 1994), 36 (Box 11)
- Mattan: The Carpet, 37 (Box 11)
- Single Payer, Across the Nation, 1 (Box 12)
  moved from box 23 to box 12 during the reorganization of the collection
- We do the work / Welcome Home / Free Trade Impact: NAFTA, 2 (Box 12)
- Zoned for Slavery - The Child Behind the Label / National Labor Committee, 3 (Box 12)
- Prison Labor/Prison Blues: We Do The Work, 4 (Box 12)
- Labor Institute of Public Affairs / Interview with William Gould, Chair NLRB, 5 (Box 12)
- The True Cost of NAFTA / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 6 (Box 12)
- Mattan / The Carpet - Short Version, 7 (Box 12)
- Stand UP Campaign News Conference, August 21, 1995, 8 (Box 12)
- AFL-CIO, CUTS :30 TV Spot // Greer, Margolis, Mitchell, Burns & Associates, 9 (Box 12)
- Get the Message? Get Out the Vote!, 10 (Box 12)
- Get the Message? Get Out the Vote!, 11 (Box 12)
- People's Inaugural, 12 (Box 12)
- Import Rally / Charlotte, N.C.; June 19, 1985, 13 (Box 12)
- The Battle is Over But the War Goes On, 14 (Box 12)
- ACTWU Spot; 2.Rap Master Ronnie, 15 (Box 12)
- We Are Driven, 16 (Box 12)
- Dying for a Job: Workers Stories About Safety: A Dialogue with Secretary of Labor Robert Reich / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 17 (Box 12)
- In-house Polling: Media Resources, 18 (Box 12)